[{"answer": " Ready for the last day, Luke", "docId": "06-04", "aSentId": 14, "question": "", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " I am really ready for a break from school.  It has been a tough first semester fo", "docId": "06-04", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Ready for the last day, Luke", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Probably just a review and then the teacher evaluations at the end", "docId": "06-04", "aSentId": 19, "question": " I am really ready for a break from school.  It has been a tough first semester fo", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " Teacher evaluations?  What do you mean", "docId": "06-04", "aSentId": 20, "question": " Probably just a review and then the teacher evaluations at the end", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Oh, yeah.  I forgot this is your first term here.  Well, at the end of each class w", "docId": "06-04", "aSentId": 21, "question": " Teacher evaluations?  What do you mean", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " Really", "docId": "06-04", "aSentId": 25, "question": " Oh, yeah.  I forgot this is your first term here.  Well, at the end of each class w", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": " Yeah", "docId": "06-04", "aSentId": 26, "question": " Really", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " What kind of things do we rate them on", "docId": "06-04", "aSentId": 27, "question": " Yeah", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " Umm, for the professor we rate them on things like preparation, enthusiasm", "docId": "06-04", "aSentId": 31, "question": " What kind of things do we rate them on", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " Oh", "docId": "06-04", "aSentId": 35, "question": " Umm, for the professor we rate them on things like preparation, enthusiasm", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " For the class, we get to rate it on things like if it was difficult, if it was interesting", "docId": "06-04", "aSentId": 36, "question": " Oh", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " We never did anything like that in high school", "docId": "06-04", "aSentId": 41, "question": " For the class, we get to rate it on things like if it was difficult, if it was interesting", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " I know.  I didnt either.  You just do it at universities.  I guess here they car", "docId": "06-04", "aSentId": 42, "question": " We never did anything like that in high school", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " Thats pretty good.  So, what are you going to say about Professor Brown an", "docId": "06-04", "aSentId": 46, "question": " I know.  I didnt either.  You just do it at universities.  I guess here they car", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " Im going to tell the truth.  Im going to write that I thought he was a terribl", "docId": "06-04", "aSentId": 50, "question": " Thats pretty good.  So, what are you going to say about Professor Brown an", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " What?!  Professor Brown will see your name on your paper and flunk you", "docId": "06-04", "aSentId": 54, "question": " Im going to tell the truth.  Im going to write that I thought he was a terribl", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " Ha Ha.  No, the evaluations are anonymous.  We dont write our names o", "docId": "06-04", "aSentId": 55, "question": " What?!  Professor Brown will see your name on your paper and flunk you", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " Wont he recognize your handwriting", "docId": "06-04", "aSentId": 59, "question": " Ha Ha.  No, the evaluations are anonymous.  We dont write our names o", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " No, after the department collects all of the evaluations, the secretary type", "docId": "06-04", "aSentId": 60, "question": " Wont he recognize your handwriting", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " Oh, OK.  So, I guess we can be totally honest and it wont affect our grade, right", "docId": "06-04", "aSentId": 64, "question": " No, after the department collects all of the evaluations, the secretary type", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Right.  The department really wants to know what we think.  How would you rat", "docId": "06-04", "aSentId": 65, "question": " Oh, OK.  So, I guess we can be totally honest and it wont affect our grade, right", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": "  Well, I didnt think he was that bad.  I guess Id say he was an average teacher", "docId": "06-04", "aSentId": 69, "question": " Right.  The department really wants to know what we think.  How would you rat", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " It sounds like you liked him more than me", "docId": "06-04", "aSentId": 70, "question": "  Well, I didnt think he was that bad.  I guess Id say he was an average teacher", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " Maybe", "docId": "06-04", "aSentId": 71, "question": " It sounds like you liked him more than me", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " I forgot to tell you too  theres an online site where you can go and rate you", "docId": "06-04", "aSentId": 72, "question": " Maybe", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " ratemyprofessors.com", "docId": "06-04", "aSentId": 80, "question": " I forgot to tell you too  theres an online site where you can go and rate you", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " Yeah.  Its cool because you can go and look at the professor ratings on that sit", "docId": "06-04", "aSentId": 81, "question": " ratemyprofessors.com", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " I should check that out for next term", "docId": "06-04", "aSentId": 85, "question": " Yeah.  Its cool because you can go and look at the professor ratings on that sit", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " Yeah, you should", "docId": "06-04", "aSentId": 86, "question": " I should check that out for next term", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " I guess we should go sit down now; it looks like class is about to start", "docId": "06-04", "aSentId": 87, "question": " Yeah, you should", "qSentId": 86},{"answer": " OK.  Dont forget  be honest on your evaluation", "docId": "06-04", "aSentId": 88, "question": " I guess we should go sit down now; it looks like class is about to start", "qSentId": 87},{"answer": " Dont worry, I will", "docId": "06-04", "aSentId": 89, "question": " OK.  Dont forget  be honest on your evaluation", "qSentId": 88}]
